[
    {
        "question": "She agreed ____ the job as soon as possible.",
        "A": "start",
        "B": "starting",
        "C": "starts",
        "D": "to start",
        "answer": "to start"
    },
    {
        "question": "he TV program was so ____ that I felt asleep.",
        "A": "surprising",
        "B": "tired",
        "C": "annoyed",
        "D": "boring",
        "answer": "boring"
    },
    {
        "question": "There were   ____ people at the party! There was nowhere to dance.",
        "A": "so many",
        "B": "such a",
        "C": "such",
        "D": "so much",
        "answer": "so many"
    },
    {
        "question": "I hate being late. I like to arrive ___time.",
        "A": "by",
        "B": "on",
        "C": "at",
        "D": "for",
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "question": "I'm going to bed when this TV program_____",
        "A": "ended",
        "B": "will end",
        "C": "is going to end",
        "D": "ends",
        "answer": "ends"
    },
    {
        "question": "We arrived______ the station five minutes late.",
        "A": "to",
        "B": "at",
        "C": "for",
        "D": "on",
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "question": "She ______work on Monday. It is her day off.",
        "A": "must",
        "B": "have to",
        "C": "doesn't have to",
        "D": "didnâ€™t",
        "answer": "doesn't have to"
    },
    {
        "question": "She was very ill and_____ died, but fortunately, she got better.",
        "A": "nearly",
        "B": "carefully",
        "C": "too",
        "D": "usually",
        "answer": "nearly"
    },
    {
        "question": "He is one of the_____ boys in the class.",
        "A": "funnier",
        "B": "most funny",
        "C": "more funny",
        "D": "funniest",
        "answer": "funniest"
    },
    {
        "question": "You have the same hobby _______Jack.",
        "A": "as",
        "B": "with",
        "C": "So",
        "D": "like",
        "answer": "as"
    },
    {
        "question": "The hotel __________we stayed was very comfortable.",
        "A": "who",
        "B": "where",
        "C": "Whose",
        "D": "when",
        "answer": "where"
    },
    {
        "question": "I didn't like this city. The streets were so dirty and the air was so______",
        "A": "pollute",
        "B": "polluted",
        "C": "to pollution",
        "D": "polluting",
        "answer": "polluted"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is the place in  ________ he was born.",
        "A": "which",
        "B": "whose",
        "C": "where",
        "D": "there",
        "answer": "which"
    },
    {
        "question": "Peter enjoyed_________ to the zoo when he was small.",
        "A": "taken",
        "B": "being taken",
        "C": "taking",
        "D": "to take",
        "answer": "being taken"
    },
    {
        "question": "When she called, I_____ a bath.",
        "A": "am having",
        "B": "was having",
        "C": "were having",
        "D": "had",
        "answer": "was having"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rolls Royce cars ___ in England.",
        "A": "were made",
        "B": "is made",
        "C": "makes",
        "D": "are made",
        "answer": "are made"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there___ traffic in your town?",
        "A": "A many",
        "B": "a few",
        "C": "some",
        "D": "much",
        "answer": "much"
    },
    {
        "question": "Last year, we managed________ a new house.",
        "A": "bought",
        "B": "to buying",
        "C": "to buy",
        "D": "buy",
        "answer": "to buy"
    },
    {
        "question": "I'm looking forward______ more free time",
        "A": "to have",
        "B": "having",
        "C": "to having",
        "D": "of having",
        "answer": "to having"
    },
    {
        "question": "Please ask______ help if you want.",
        "A": "for",
        "B": "to",
        "C": "or",
        "D": "in",
        "answer": "for"
    }
]